foxmovies.com 2013-06-02

# 20th Century Fox

## Privacy Policy

### Effective September 30, 2011:

Summary of the Fox Filmed Entertainment Privacy Policy: 

  1. **INTRODUCTION -** The Introduction identifies Fox Filmed Entertainment, the basic Services it offers and provides a brief overview of what this Privacy Policy covers.
  2. **SUBMISSION AND COLLECTION OF INFORMATION -** This section addresses the types of information that Fox Filmed Entertainment collects directly from users and the collection of non-personally identifiable information via cookies and related technologies by, and on behalf of, Fox Filmed Entertainment and third parties.
  3. **NOTICE AND CHOICE -** This section provides information on users' options to control how their information is collected and used, how Fox Filmed Entertainment notifies users about future Privacy Policy changes, where Fox Filmed Entertainment stores data, and third-party websites that may link to the Fox FE Services.
  4. **USE AND DISCLOSURE -** This section describes how Fox Filmed Entertainment uses your information to provide and manage the Fox FE Services, including when Fox Filmed Entertainment may disclose your information to third parties that assist Fox Filmed Entertainment in providing those services.
  5. **SECURITY -** This section describes Fox Filmed Entertainment's security measures.
  6. **USER CONTROL AND ACCOUNT CANCELATION -** This section informs users how to access and change their personal information stored by the Fox FE Services, and how to cancel their accounts.
  7. **CONTACT US -** This section instructs users how to contact Fox Filmed Entertainment.
  8. **ADDITIONAL PROVISIONS FOR CHILDREN'S PRIVACY -** This section describes additional privacy protections for Fox FE Services directed to children under 13.

#### 1\. INTRODUCTION

Top

Fox Filmed Entertainment, Inc. ("Fox FE" or "we") operates FoxMovies.com, FoxSearchlight.com, and other entertainment websites featuring content related to Fox Filmed Entertainment movies (the "Sites"). The services Fox FE offers include the Sites and any other features, content, or applications offered from time to time by Fox FE in connection with the Sites, including when they are accessed via the Internet, mobile or other device (collectively, the "Fox FE Services"). Fox FE is part of the United States based operations of News Corporation.

Some of our online activities are directed to children under 13 and in those instances, we provide additional privacy protections. To read about these additional protections please see Section 8 below.

This Privacy Policy applies to all users. This Privacy Policy describes the collection and use of users' personal information on the Fox FE Services. It also describes generally Fox FE‘s practices for handling non-personally identifiable information (e.g., interests, demographics and site usage) to the extent such information is associated with a particular user or user account.

#### 2\. SUBMISSION AND COLLECTION OF INFORMATION ON FOX FE SERVICES

Top

 _User Submitted Information_

**Registration Information** is the information that users must provide to Fox FE at registration for or upon subscription to a Fox FE Service, for example, to create an account, enter a contest, promotion or sweepstake, receive a newsletter, play a game or take a survey.

**Public Information and Posts** consist of your your posts and comments on the Fox FE Services, for example, in comments, forums or blogs. Your Public Information and Posts are always public, which means they are available to everyone and may be displayed in search results both on the Fox FE Services and on external search engines.

_Fox FE Collected Information_

**Fox FE Site Activity Information.** When users access the Fox FE Services, we may collect certain non-personally identifiable information about those visits. For example, in order to permit your connection to the Fox FE Services, our servers receive and record information about your computer and browser, including potentially your IP address, browser type, and other software or hardware information. If you access the Fox FE Services from a mobile or other device, we may collect a unique device identifier assigned to that device or other transactional information for that device in order to serve content to it. We also may use cookies and other tracking technologies (including browser cookies, pixels, beacons, and Adobe Flash technology including cookies), which are comprised of small bits of data that often include an anonymous unique identifier. Websites send this data to your browser when you first request a web page and then store the data on your computer so Fox FE can access information when you make subsequent requests for pages from that site. We may use these technologies to collect and store information about your usage of Fox FE Services, such as pages you have visited, search queries you have run, and advertisements you have seen. Fox FE may also use cookies and similar tools to relate your use of the Fox FE Services to personal information obtained from you or a reputable third party. For example, if you have asked us to provide you information about our upcoming products or promotions, cookie and/or click stream data about your activities on the Sites may allow us to limit the materials we provide you to items we think you will find interesting, based on your prior online activities and preferences.

Third parties that support the Fox FE Services by serving advertisements or providing services, such as allowing users to share content and post comments or tracking aggregate site usage statistics, may also use these technologies to collect similar information. Fox FE does not control these third-party technologies and their use is governed by the privacy policies of third parties using such technologies. For more information about third-party ad networks that use these technologies, see [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/). Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies, but you can change your settings to notify you when a cookie is being set or updated, or to block cookies altogether. Please consult the "Help" section of your browser for more information (e.g., <http://windows.microsoft.com/en-US/windows-vista/Block-or-allow-cookies>). Users can manage the use of Flash technologies, including cookies, with the Flash management tools available at Adobe's website, see <http://www.adobe.com/products/flashplayer/security/privacy_policy/faq.html>. Please note that by blocking any or all cookies you may not have access to certain features or personalization available through the Fox FE Services.

**Third Parties.** To improve the quality of the Fox FE Services, we may supplement the information we collect with information from third parties. If you access the Fox FE Services through a third-party connection or log-in, for example, through your Facebook account, we may also collect your user ID and/or user name associated with that third-party service, or any information you have made public in connection with that service or which the third party shares with partner services.

#### 3\. NOTICE & CHOICE

Top

 **Means of Notice.** This Privacy Policy is the primary means by which Fox FE provides you with notice about its collection and use of your information.

**Privacy Policy Changes.** Fox FE may modify this Privacy Policy as necessary. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy that expand our rights to use your personal information, we will notify you to seek your consent through email or a prominent posting on the Fox FE Services.

**Location of Data.** The Fox FE Services are hosted in the United States. If you are a user located outside the United States, you understand and consent to having any personal information you provide transferred to, processed, and stored in the United States and other countries where data protection and other privacy laws may not offer the same level of protection as in your jurisdiction, such as the European Union. This includes the use of cookies and other tracking technologies as described above. As a result, please read this Privacy Policy with care.

**Linked Services.** The Fox FE Services may also be linked to sites or services operated by Fox FE affiliates (i.e., that are part of the News America Group: "Affiliated Companies") or third parties, and may carry advertisements or offer content, functionality, games, newsletters, stores, contests or sweepstakes, ticket sales, or applications developed and maintained by third parties. Fox FE is not responsible for the privacy practices of any such third parties, and once you submit information directly to a third party, leave the Fox FE Services via a link, enable a third-party service, or click an advertisement, you should check the applicable privacy policy of that third-party. Additionally, although all Affiliated Companies adhere to the News Corporation corporate Privacy Principles, users who visit an Affiliated Company site should still refer to its separate privacy policy, which may differ in some respects from this Privacy Policy.

#### 4\. USE AND DISCLOSURE

Top

 _Information Made Public Through Use of The Services_

User's Public Information and Posts are publicly available to everyone including other users of the Service, search engines, advertisers and anyone else with access to the Fox FE Services.

Use and Disclosure of Information

We only share your non-public personal information with non-affiliated third parties when we believe sharing is permitted by you or authorized by this Privacy Policy. We may share your personal information with Affiliated Companies.

We use the information we collect from and about users for the following purposes:

**To provide and manage the Fox FE Services.** We use the information we collect from and about users to provide the Fox FE Services and features to you, which may include to measure and improve those services and features, to personalize your experience by delivering relevant content, advertising and marketing messages, to allow you to participate in online games, contests or promotions or to provide you with customer support, and to respond to inquiries. We may use aggregated, anonymous data about use of and activity on the Fox FE Services to assist us in this regard and such data is not subject to this Privacy Policy.

**To contact you.** Fox FE may periodically send promotional materials (e.g., newsletters) or notifications related to the Fox FE Services to the email address you provided to us upon subscription or registration to the Fox FE Services. If you want to stop receiving promotional materials from Fox FE, you can follow the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. There are certain service notification emails that you may not opt-out of as long as you are a member, such as notifications of changes to the Fox FE Services or policies.

**To deliver relevant advertising.** We may use the information you provide to us, and information we collect about your use of the Fox FE Services through cookies and other technologies, to assist us in delivering you relevant ads when you visit the Fox FE Services. We may work with third-party advertising networks and advertisers who help deliver these ads to you. We do not share your non-public personal information with these third parties, but we may share anonymized or aggregated information with them to improve the relevancy of the ads you see on the Fox FE Services. As noted above, these third-party advertising networks and advertisers may also use cookies and similar technologies to collect and track non-personally identifiable information such as demographic information, aggregated information, and Internet activity to assist them in delivering advertising that is more relevant to your interests. To find out more about third-party online advertising and to opt out of this type of advertising, visit the Network Advertising Initiative website <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. Fox FE also shares non-personally identifiable demographic and interest information associated with your account with third-party advertising networks to assist them in delivering relevant ads on the Fox FE Services.

**To protect the rights of Fox FE and our users.** There may be instances when Fox FE may disclose user information without providing notice or choice, including situations where Fox FE has a good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary in order to: (i) protect or defend the legal rights or property of Fox FE, our Affiliated Companies or their employees, agents and contractors (including enforcement of our agreements); (ii) protect the safety and security of users of the Fox FE Services or members of the public; (iii) protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; or (iv) comply with the law or legal process. We may retain backup information related to your use of the Fox FE Services on our servers for fraud detection or to comply with applicable law or our internal security policies.

**To complete a merger or sale of assets.** If Fox FE sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of its assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or transfer of all or a material part of its business, Fox FE may transfer your information to the party or parties involved in the transaction as part of that transaction.

#### 5\. SECURITY

Top

Fox FE uses commercially reasonable administrative, technical, personnel and physical measures to safeguard user information in its possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification.

#### 6\. USER CONTROL AND ACCOUNT CANCELATION

Top

If you would like to review your personal information in our records, change any personal information or user preferences previously submitted, please go to Member Center. If you would like to cancel your account, please contact us at feedbackus@fox.com. We may also retain backup information related to your account on our servers for some time after cancelation for fraud detection or to comply with applicable law or our internal security policies. Because of the nature of caching technology, your account may not be instantly inaccessible to others, and there may be a delay in the removal of the content from elsewhere on the Internet and from search engines. In addition, remember that even after you cancel your account, copies of some information from your account may remain viewable in some circumstances - where, for example, you or another user have shared information with a third-party application or website.

#### 7\. CONTACT US

Top

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact Fox FE at:

Email: [feedbackus@fox.com](mailto:%20feedbackus@fox.com)

Mail:  
Privacy Officer  
P.O. Box 900  
Beverly Hills, CA 90212

#### 8\. ADDITIONAL PROVISIONS FOR CHILDREN'S PRIVACY

Top

We at Fox FE understand that the Internet presents an opportunity for us to reach the public in new and exciting ways with information about our programming, fun games, exciting sweepstakes and contests, email, chat rooms, bulletin boards and other forms of interactivity. Fox FE also recognizes the privacy concerns of parents (including other legal guardians), and the importance of protecting the privacy of the information collected from children at the Fox FE Services. Parents of children under 13 who visit the Fox FE Services can be confident that any personal information that may be provided to the Fox FE Services will be collected and maintained in accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA"). Fox FE encourages children to check with their parents before using the Fox FE Services and encourages parents to supervise their children's activities online and to participate with their children's online activities whenever possible.

**Collection and Use of Personal Information from Children Under 13.**

When a visitor to the Fox FE Services is under the age of 13, Fox FE does not require the disclosure of more personal information than is reasonably necessary for him or her to participate in an activity as a condition of such participation.

Fox FE may collect and use different types of personal information submitted to the Fox FE Services by children under 13 in a variety of ways, which are described below. In each instance, we comply with the parental consent requirements of COPPA.

(i) We may collect a child's email address in connection with a contest, sweepstakes or game for the sole purpose of communicating with the child on a one-time-only basis (i.e., to contact a sweepstakes winner). This information will not be used to re-contact the child, and will be deleted from our records when the contest or game is over. Parental consent is obtained before we send a prize to any winner under 13.

(ii) We may collect a child's email address in order to respond more than once to a child's specific request. For example, the child may want to subscribe to an online newsletter or receive other online communications from Fox FE. In these instances Fox FE will also obtain a parent's email address along with the child's. Before any further contact with the child, Fox FE will send an email to the parent (A) notifying him or her we have collected the child's email address in order to respond more than once to the child's request for a subscription, information, etc.; (B) informing the parent that he or she can refuse us permission to contact the child, and how to do so; and (C) informing the parent that if he or she does not respond to the email within one (1) week, Fox FE may use the child's information for the purpose for which it was submitted. Under no circumstances will the child be allowed to participate without giving a parent's email address.

(iii) We may collect a child's personal information (including name, email address, mailing address and phone number) for such activities as chats, forums, surveys, games, bulletin boards, requests for suggestions, subscription registrations, content submissions, requests for products or services, or requests for additional information. In these instances we will initially collect only the child's name and online contact information and the email address of the child's parent. Before using this information for any purpose, we will send the parent an email that (A) informs the parent that we wish to collect and use the child's personal information and need the parent's consent to do so, and (B) provides the parent with a link to access this Privacy Policy, which describes our information collection and use policies as required by COPPA. Fox FE will ask the parent to provide consent by return email. Upon receipt of the email consent, we will send the parent a confirming email.

(iv) We may collect a child's name and email to protect the safety of a child who is participating in the Fox FE Services. In these instances, we will notify the parent and give the parent an opportunity to prevent further use of this information.

(v) We may collect a child's name and email address to the extent reasonably necessary to protect the security of this Fox FE Services, to protect against liability, to respond to law enforcement or as required or permitted by law and disclose such information to third parties where it is necessary for such purpose. Information collected for these reasons will not be used for any other purpose.

(vi) We may share your child's personal information with service providers that provide support for the FOX FE Services by, for example, providing, or assisting us in providing, the FOX FE Services to your child. If we plan to share your child's personal information with a third party for any reason other than to provide these or other internal support services, we will notify you and give you the opportunity to opt-out of such disclosure. Parents may consent to Fox FE's collection and use of a child's personal information without consenting to the disclosure of the information to third parties other than such service providers.

(vii) If Fox FE sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of its assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or transfer of all or a material part of its business, Fox FE may transfer your child's information to the party or parties involved in the transaction as part of that transaction.

**Linked Services.**

The Fox FE Services may also be linked to sites or services operated by Affiliated Companies or third parties, and may carry advertisements or offer content, functionality, games, newsletters, stores, contests or sweepstakes, ticket sales, or applications developed and maintained by third parties. Those sites or services, which are not controlled by Fox FE, may collect personal information from your child. Parents should therefore check the relevant site's privacy policy to understand how it collects and uses children's personal information. Fox FE is not responsible for the privacy practices of any such third parties. Additionally, although all Affiliated Companies adhere to the News Corporation corporate Privacy Principles, parents should still refer to the Affiliated Company's site or service's separate privacy policy, which may differ in some respects from this Privacy Policy. Fox FE will not knowingly receive any personal information from another site from a child under the age of 13 if that site does not follow the requirements of COPPA.

**Reviewing and Making Changes to Personal Information Collected from Children Under 13.**

Parents of children under age 13 may review or delete personal information about their children from our records at any time. If you would like your child's personal information deleted, please contact us at feedbackus@fox.com. We will delete your child's information from our database if you so request.

If you would like to review the personal information in our records submitted by your child, or change any personal information previously submitted by your child, please go to Member Center and follow the instructions.
